[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Russian volcano, located on the Kamchatka Peninsula, is one of the most active volcanoes on the planet.", "correct_answer": "Avachinsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Elbrus", "Anik Mountain", "Sikhote-Alin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the location of the worlds largest particle physics laboratory, established in 1954?", "correct_answer": "In neither of them", "incorrect_answers": ["In the EU", "Both have laboratories of equal size.", "In the US"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The quote, I wont kill you, but I dont have to save you is from what movie?", "correct_answer": "Batman Begins", "incorrect_answers": ["Matrix Reloaded", "Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl", "Lord of the Rings, Two Towers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1983 William Friedkin released this movie that was presented as a latter-day Dr. Strangelove and was blasted by critics.", "correct_answer": "Deal of the Century", "incorrect_answers": ["Finders Keepers", "Once Upon A Time In America", "Cannonball Run"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hammer v. Dagenhart  was an important Supreme Court case, which dealt what topic?", "correct_answer": "Child labor vis-a-vis interstate commerce", "incorrect_answers": ["Segragation", "The right to privacy", "Abortion rights"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the Spanish dish called Escalivada, which originated in Catalonia, Spain?", "correct_answer": "Salad", "incorrect_answers": ["Dessert", "Soup", "Boiled meats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the Warden in the hit movie The Shawshank Redemption ?", "correct_answer": "Samuel Norton", "incorrect_answers": ["Byron Hadley", "Ellis Redding", "Spencer Heywood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1985, Shasta  was acquired by the Royal Crown Cola Corp., which also owned the Faygo line of soft drinks.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He directed the movie Bubble which starred unprofessional actors.", "correct_answer": "Steven Soderbergh", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Greengrass", "Lee Grant", "Sike Jonze"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would one find the worlds largest vulture?", "correct_answer": "The Andes", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africa", "Australia", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what date was the planet Neptune discovered?", "correct_answer": "September 23, 1846.", "incorrect_answers": ["August 19, 1901.", "May 3, 1865.", "December 19, 1888."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term a positive review of systems refer to?", "correct_answer": "To every symptom question, the patient says yes", "incorrect_answers": ["The patient reviews his symptoms well", "A favorable review of systems", "To every symptom question, the patient says no"]}]